{
    "id": "39d020a40d7d4fb69bd8df4f7afe2114",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Sid can play tennis as ................................ as his brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b473bcc0c01a41d9be8c76c8f254d7aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "The match had hardly begun .................................. it started raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c05c7b32e86b41aaaf679234fcb2a4fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ...................................... a mistake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sure",
                "surely"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "529f3fe3cd8c4005872b9e78e9adf3a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He talks more .......................................... than his brother. Needless to say, he is the more popular of the two.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pleasant",
                "pleasantly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60c4aae6ff73408da527c93c9b5469b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "When you become a parent, you will think .................................... about children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "different",
                "differently"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c2add74ec654be5ad988c117ad8be94"
        },
        {
            "question": "I felt ...................................... about not having won the championship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1be0dfe2e4fb4963aa34dbd8c283b2ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "Winning is not ...................................... as important as playing well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "near",
                "nearly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b6d6d3dc73564cc39057f4b4afddf4e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "His behavior seemed a little ............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "oddly",
                "odd"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "49096b1e19294b59ab7436b0d5fdeda0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He didnâ€™t run ....................................... enough to qualify for the race.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7a6d7a0119d24ac59ab57646838e91be"
        },
        {
            "question": "We could ............................................ see the snow-capped mountains at a distance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "clear",
                "clearly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17139f107c18486cabc32508e6528d2b"
        }
    ]
}